

Sutrishna Anjoy

Site Reliability Engineer

• Profiles •

in <u>sutrisna-anjoy</u> LinkedIn

sutrisnaanjoy19 GitHub

o Skills o

Orchestration

Advanced

Kubernetes, Kustomize, Helm, ArgoCD, Docker

CI/CD

Advanced

Jenkins, GitLab, AR, Spinnaker

Monitoring & Alerting

Intermediate

Prometheus, Grafana, Alertmanager, Pagerduty, ELK

Others

Git, VSCode, Terraform, Google Cloud, AWS, Python, Groovy, C++, Bash, Linux, Networking, OS

• Awards •

MTech Topper

IIEST

Dec 2022

Publications

Lung Cancer detection using 2D CNN

Springer

Jun 2022

In this paper, we use 2D convolutional neural networks to detect malignant nodules from CT scan images. We use modified *VGG16* for the identification of lung cancer.

Springer URL

Summary

Site Reliability Engineer with 2 years of experience expertly managing and optimizing **Kubernetes** clusters on **Google Cloud**. Dedicated to ensuring high availability, scalability, and performance, with a knack for crafting efficient **Jenkins** pipelines to streamline deployment processes.

Experience

Media.net

Site Reliability Engineer

Mumbai, IN

Jul 2022 to Present

- Monitoring and maintaining multiple GKE clusters across regions.
- Analysis and planning of reducing cost of existing cloud resources used in the projects.
- Setting Logstash pipelines, Kibana alerts, watchers for Developers.
- Writing Jenkins pipelines to automate some of our repeating tasks.
- Used technologies like Kubernetes, Kustomize, Helm, Google Cloud
 (GKE, AR), ArgoCD & Rollouts, ELK, Jenkins, Docker, Git.

Media.net

SRE-Intern

Mumbai, IN

Feb 2022 - Jun 2022

- Understanding Linux, Networking, Distributed systems, Virtualization.
- Learning and practicing SRE concepts like Monitoring, CI/CD, containerization, orchestration.
- Reviewing and helping out in maintenance of GKE, ELK clusters.

Education

Computer Science and Engineering 9.63 CGPA

Masters in Technology

Sep 2020 - Jun 2022

- Area of study: Deep learning.
- Wrote thesis on Identification of Lung Cancer Nodules from CT images using 2D Convolutional Neural Networks.
- https://www.iiests.ac.in/